(Amy:)Do you think he'd let me
draw a syringe full of his blood?
(Penny:)Hmm. He's not crazy about needles.
(Penny:)But if you get him to go jogging,
it'll just pour out of his nose.
I don't think I can meet the girI
who was always mean to me.
(Bernadette:)Tammy Bodnick.
One time while I was in gym class...
(Bernadette:)...she stole all my clothes
and left an eIf costume in my Iocker.
- Oh, that's awful.
- Worst part was it was too big.
(Amy:)That's nothing. In ninth grade,
the girls put Rogaine in my hand lotion.
(Amy:)Within six months,
the nicknames began to fly.
(Amy:)I think the one that hurt the most
was Gorilla Fingers Fowler.
Oh. Wow, you poor thing.
(Bernadette:)What about you?
Oh, I don't know. My school
was a nice place. We didn't have bullies.
(Amy:)Come on, no one ever gave anyone
mean nicknames, or picked on them...
(Amy:)...or put gum in their hairy knuckles
so the nurse had get it out?
No, we weren't really Iike that.
(Penny:)We played pranks on each other,
but it was never mean.